<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Creating a grid job description">
   <intro href="/eu.geclipse.doc.user/html/gettingstarted/CreatingaJob.html">
      <description>
          This cheat sheet will show you how to create a grid job description.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item title="Open the g-Eclipse user perspective">
      <description>
          If you are not already in the g-Eclipse user perspective, in the main menu
          select <b>Window &gt; Open Perspective &gt; g-Eclipse (User)</b> or click
          on the &quot;Click to Perform&quot; link below.
      </description>
	  <action
	          pluginId="org.eclipse.ui.cheatsheets"
			  class="org.eclipse.ui.internal.cheatsheets.actions.OpenPerspective"
			  param1="eu.geclipse.ui.userPerspective"/>
   </item>
   <item title="Create your job description file using the g-Eclipse Grid Job Wizard.">
      <description>
		Select <b>File &gt; New &gt; Job Description</b>. (Alternatively, you may right-click in the 
		<b>Grid Project</b> view and choose <b>New &gt; Job Description</b>.)  
		This wizard will generate a file in the Job Submission Description Language (JSDL).
		<br/>Choose the 'Job Description' folder of your Grid Project and type in the name 
		you would like to give your jsdl file. <br/>
		Click <b>Next</b>.<br/>
      </description>
      <!--<action confirm="true"
	          pluginId="eu.geclipse.ui"
			  class="eu.geclipse.ui.views.gexplorer.GExplorerView.NewConnectionWizardAction"
			  />-->
   </item>
   <item title="Specify the executable.">
      <description>
          Choose the executable you would like to run in your job by locating it 
          with the <b>Browse</b> button.
          Here, you can also give your job a name and a short description.<br/>
          Click <b>Next</b>.<br/>
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Specify the input files.">
      <description>
          Choose the input files required by your executable by clicking on
          <b>Add file...</b> to add it to the list. <br/>If your executable requires 
          no input files, leave the list empty.
          Click <b>Next</b>.<br/>
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Specify the output files.">
      <description>
          Choose the output files produced by your executable by clicking 
          <b>Add file...</b> to add it to the list. You can specify multiple 
          output files with associated settings. <br/>If your executable produces 
          no output files, leave the list empty. 
          Click <b>Next</b>.<br/>
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Specify Environment Variables">
      <description>
          Specify any Environment Variables required for the job to run. <br/>
          Click <b>Finish</b> to complete the wizard. Verify that your new jsdl file 
          is in the 'Job Description' folder in your Grid Project.<br/>
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
      