<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Creating an Authentication Token">
   <intro href="/eu.geclipse.doc.user/html/gettingstarted/AuthenticationTokens.html">
      <description>
          This cheat sheet will show you how to create your authentication token.<br/>
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item title="Open the g-Eclipse perspective" skip="true">
      <description>
          If you're not already in the g-Eclipse user perspective, in the main menu
          select <b>Window &gt; Open Perspective &gt; g-Eclipse (User)</b> or click
          on the &quot;Click to Perform&quot; link below.
      </description>
	  <action
	          pluginId="org.eclipse.ui.cheatsheets"
			  class="org.eclipse.ui.internal.cheatsheets.actions.OpenPerspective"
			  param1="eu.geclipse.ui.userPerspective"/>
   </item>
   <item title="Select the Authentication Tokens View" skip="true">
      <description>
          Select the <b>Authentication Tokens</b> tab in the bottom panel view.<br/>
      </description>
      <command serialization="org.eclipse.ui.views.showView(org.eclipse.ui.views.showView.viewId=eu.geclipse.ui.views.authenticationTokenView)"/>
   </item>
   <item title="Click the New icon" dialog="true" skip="true">
      <description>
          Click the <b>New</b> icon located in the top right corner of the 
          <b>Authentication Tokens</b> panel view.<br/>
      </description>
      <action confirm="true"
          pluginId="eu.geclipse.ui"
		  class="eu.geclipse.ui.cheatsheets.OpenAuthTokenDialogAction"/>
   </item>
   <item title="Choose the Token Type" >
      <description>
          Once you clicked the new icon, a <b>New Authentication Token</b> window 
          will appear. Make your selection by choosing between <b>Grid Proxy</b> 
          and <b>VOMS Proxy</b> and click the <b>Next</b> button. <br/>Note 
          that you may bypass this dialog box if you carefully click the downward 
          pointing arrow of the <b>New</b> icon. In this case, the kinds of proxy 
          appear in a pull down menu, allowing you to make the selection directly 
          from here.<br/>
      </description>
   </item>
   <item perform-when="true" title="Grid Proxy: Locate Your Certificate">
      <description>
          After clicking the <b>Next</b> button, the <b>Grid Proxy</b> dialog box 
          will appear. Specify the location of your key and certificate and enter 
          your key passphrase. In this dialog box, you may also adjust how long 
          will the proxy be valid. By default, this <b>Proxy Lifetime</b> value 
          is set to 1 day.<br/>
      </description>
   </item>
   <item perform-when="true" title="VOMS Proxy: Locate Your Certificate">
      <description>
          Sorry, not yet implemented.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Create Your Token">
      <description>
          Press finish and your proxy will be validated and will appear as an entry 
          in the <b>Authentication Tokens</b> panel view. <br/>
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Activate Your Token">
      <description>  
          Activate this token by first clicing on the token entry in the 
          <b>Activation Tokens</b> panel view (this makes button with a 
          pedlock icon visible) and then click the <b>Activation</b> button on the top right
          of this panel view.<br/>
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
      