<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Creating a new g-Eclipse Grid Project">
   <intro href="/eu.geclipse.doc.user/html/gettingstarted/NewProjectWizard.html">
      <description>
          This cheat sheet will show you how to create a new g-Eclipse Grid Project.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item title="Open the g-Eclipse user perspective" skip="true">
      <description>
          If you are not already in the g-Eclipse user perspective, in the main menu
          select <b>Window &gt; Open Perspective &gt; g-Eclipse (User)</b> or click
          on the &quot;Click to Perform&quot; link below.
      </description>
      <command serialization="org.eclipse.ui.perspectives.showPerspective(org.eclipse.ui.perspectives.showPerspective.perspectiveId=eu.geclipse.ui.userPerspective)" confirm="false"/>
   </item>
   <item title="Select the Grid Project View" skip="true">
      <description>
          Select the Grid Project View on your g-Eclipse Workbench.
      </description>
      <command serialization="org.eclipse.ui.views.showView(org.eclipse.ui.views.showView.viewId=eu.geclipse.ui.views.gridProjectView)"/>
   </item>
   <item title="Launch the Grid Project Wizard" dialog="true" skip="true">
      <description>
          Right-click into that view and select <b>New &gt; Grid Project</b> to launch the wizard.
      </description>
      <command confirm="false" serialization="org.eclipse.ui.newWizard(newWizardId=eu.geclipse.ui.wizards.gridProjectWizard)"/>
   </item>
   <item title="Basic Information">
   	  <description>Step through the pages in the Grid Project Wizard.</description>
      <subitem label="Name and Location">
      	  Specify the name you want your grid project to be called and the location where you want to 
          store it's settings on your local harddisk. For the location you may accept 
          the default settings. Then click the <b>Next</b> button.
      </subitem>
      <subitem label="VO">
      	  Select your VO from the list and click the <b>Next</b> button.
      	  Or, if you have no VO available in the list, you can create a new one by clicking on 
      	  the <b>New VO</b> button, selecting the type of VO and clicking the <b>Next</b> button.
      	<subitem label="New VO">
      	  Enter the name for your VO, host, port, host DN, Information System Endpoint, 
      	  and the VO server URL and click the <b>Finish</b> Button. Then select your VO from the list
      	  and click <b>Next</b> to get to the last page of this wizard.
      	</subitem>
      </subitem>
      <subitem label="Referenced Project">
      	  Select the referenced project and click the <b>Finish</b> button to complete the 
      	  new grid project creation. Your newly created project will appear in the 
      	  "Grid Projects" view panel.
      </subitem>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
      