<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Downloading CA Certificates">
   <intro href="/eu.geclipse.doc.user/html/concepts/setup/cacertificates.html">
      <description>
         This cheat sheet will show you how to download and install CA certificates into g-Eclipse.<br/>
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item title="Open the CA Certificates Dialog Box" dialog="true" skip="true">
      <description>
         Click the <b>Click to Perform</b> link below to get to <b>Window &gt; Preferences &gt; g-Eclipse &gt; Security</b> Preferences dialog. This will embed this cheatsheet in the dialog so that you can continue performing the tasks while following the description in the sheatsheet.<br/>
      </description>
      <command serialization="org.eclipse.ui.window.preferences(preferencePageId=eu.geclipse.ui.internal.preference.securityPreferencePage)" returns="result" confirm="true">
      </command>
   </item>
   <item title="Add CA From Repository" dialog="true" skip="false">
      <description>
         To import a list of certificates into the g-Eclipse certificate manager, click the <b>Import...</b> button in the Security Preference Page. This opens the <b>Certificate Import Wizard</b>. There, you&apos;ll find a list of certificate repositories available from the Grid Policy Management Authorities and, in addition, the Gilda CA certificate (needed for using the Gilda training infrastructure).<br/><br/>
Select one of the listed repositories and press <b>Next</b>.  Now this repository is queried for available certificates. After a while, the certificates contained in the specified repository will be listed on the next wizard page.<br/><br/>
Now select the certificates you would like to import and click <b>Finish</b>.  The various certificates will be downloaded, unzipped and installed.<br/>
      </description>
      <command
            required="false"
            serialization="org.eclipse.ui.dialogs.openInputDialog"/>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Add CA From File">
      <description>
         Alternatively, you may import a CA Certificate from your local or remote location. <br/><br/>To do this, click the <b>Add...</b> button. This will open the Grid File dialog from which you navigate to the desired location where the CA Certificate that you want to have available is stored. <br/><br/>Select the certificate and press OK to exit the dialog. The crtificate will be installed.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Finish">
      <description>
         Complete the certificates import by pressing the OK button of the Prefereces window.
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
