<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<compositeCheatsheet name="g-Eclipse Cheatsheets">
    <taskGroup skip="true" name= "Getting Started With g-Eclipse" kind="sequence">
         <intro href="/org.eclipse.platform.doc.user/reference/ref-cheatsheets.htm">
         This set of cheat sheets will guide you through the set up process of 
         using g-Eclipse.<br/><br/>You can select a task to work on, either by following 
         the hyperlinks offered below, or by selecting a task after expanding the tree
         above.<br/><br/>The second set of tasks of this cheat sheet group, <b>Grid 
         Project View Set Up</b>, depends on the first set, <b>Preliminary Set Up</b>. 
         If you have not completed the first set, you should do so before moving on to 
         the second set. 
         <br/>Otherwise, if you are not allowed to move on even though your g-Eclipse is 
         already set up, i.e. if you have restarted the <b>Getting Started With g-Eclipse</b> 
         cheat sheet set, you may advance by skipping the individual tasks of the set 
         or skipping the whole set at once.
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>Congratulations! You have completed all the tasks required 
         before you can start interacting with the Grid!</onCompletion>
         
		<taskGroup skip="true" name= "Preliminary Set Up" kind = "set">
			<intro> First, you will learn how to set up the g-Eclipse environment. 
			<br/><br/>The tasks in this group may be started in any order.</intro>
			<onCompletion>Congratulations! You have completed the set up of the gEclipse 
			environment.</onCompletion>
			<task skip="true" kind="cheatsheet" name= "Downloading CA Certificates">
				<param name="id" value = "eu.geclipse.doc.user.downloadingCAcertificates"/>
				<param name="showIntro" value = "true"/>
				<intro>This cheat sheet walks you through the process of downloading 
				CA certificates.</intro>
				<onCompletion>Congratulations! You have succeeded in downloading 
				CA certificates.</onCompletion>
			</task>
			<task skip="true" kind="cheatsheet" name= "Creating an Authentication Token">
				<param name="showIntro" value = "true"/>
				<param name = "id" value = "eu.geclipse.doc.user.creatingAuthenticationToken" />
				<intro>This cheat sheet walks you through the process of creating an
				Authentication Token.<br/></intro>
				<onCompletion>Congratulations! You have succeeded in creating your
				Authentication Token.</onCompletion>           
			</task>
		</taskGroup>
             
		<taskGroup skip="true" name= "Grid Project Set Up" kind = "sequence">
			<intro> Next, you will learn how to set up your g-Eclipse Project View, 
			create a simple job and submit it. 
			<br/><br/>This task group is a sequence, which means that if you click on the 
			subtask "Creating a Grid Job", it will not let that task be started until 
			"Create a Grid Project" has been completed.</intro>
			<onCompletion>Congratulations! You have succeeded in submitting a job to the Grid!</onCompletion>
			<task skip="true" kind="cheatsheet" name= "Creating a Grid Project">
				<param name="showIntro" value = "true"/>
				<param name = "id" value = "eu.geclipse.doc.user.creatingAGridProject" />
				<intro>This cheat sheet guides you through the process of creating a new Grid 
				Project.</intro>
				<onCompletion>Congratulations! You have succeeded in creating a new Grid 
				Project.</onCompletion>           
			</task>   
			<task skip="true" kind="cheatsheet" name= "Creating a Grid Job">
				<param name="showIntro" value = "true"/>
				<param name = "id" value = "eu.geclipse.doc.user.creatingAJob" />
				<intro>This cheat sheet guides you through the process of creating
				a grid job.</intro>
				<onCompletion>Congratulations! You have succeeded in creating 
				a grid job.</onCompletion>           
			</task>     
			<task skip="true" kind="cheatsheet" name= "Submitting a Grid Job">
				<param name="showIntro" value = "true"/>
				<param name = "id" value = "eu.geclipse.doc.user.submittingAJob" />
				<intro>This cheat sheet guides you through the process of submitting
				a grid job.</intro>
				<onCompletion>Congratulations! You have succeeded in submitting 
				a grid job.</onCompletion>           
			</task>     
		</taskGroup>
		
    </taskGroup>
</compositeCheatsheet>