<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet title="Title">
   <intro href="/eu.geclipse.doc.user/html/gettingstarted/visualization/SpecifyingVtkPipelineContent.html">
      <description>
         This cheat sheet will show you how to further define and edit a VTK pipeline file.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item title="Open the g-Eclipse User perspective" dialog="true" skip="true">
      <description>
         If you are not already in the g-Eclipse User perspective, in the main menu
          select <b>Window &gt; Open Perspective &gt; Other...</b> and select
          <b>g-Eclipse (User)</b>. Alternatively, click on the &quot;Click to Perform&quot; 
          link below.
      </description>
      <action class="org.eclipse.ui.internal.cheatsheets.actions.OpenPerspective" pluginId="org.eclipse.ui.cheatsheets" confirm="false" param1="eu.geclipse.ui.userPerspective">
      </action>
   </item>
   <item title="Open the VTK Pipeline Editor" dialog="true" skip="true">
      <description>
         If you have closed the <b>VTK Pipeline Editor</b>, created in the previous cheatsheet, 
         double-click on your <b>.vtkpipeline</b> file to open it up again. 
      	You will see a five page editor, with the <b>Overview page</b> selected.
      	This editor will allow you to further describe your <b>VTK pipeline</b>.
      	Note that only the file location is currently used when reading the <b>VTK Pipeline
      	file</b> during rendering. All other settings will be used in later development.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Overview Page" dialog="true" skip="true">
      <description>
         The <b>Overview page</b> that also links to the additional editor pages allows you to edit the 
         main entries, which you have originally filled in with the wizard.
         If you are satisfied with the content of this page, select the next tab or click
         on the <b>DataSource</b> link.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Data Source Page" dialog="true" skip="true">
      <description>
         On this page, under the <b>Data Source Section</b>, you can change the data 
         file location, and the type of the data. Under the <b>Data Reader Section</b>, you will 
         be able to add the <b>VTK reader class</b> and set its respective parameters. 
         Now select the next tab called <b>Data Processing Page</b>.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Data Processing Page" dialog="true" skip="true">
      <description>
         On this page you will be able to change the output format.
         Now select the next tab called <b>VTK Filter Algorithm Page</b>.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="VTK Filter Algorithm Page" dialog="true" skip="true">
      <description>
         On this page you will be able to add the filter algorithm classes and 
         their attributes.
         Now select the last tab called <b>*.vtkpipeline</b>.
      </description>
   </item>
   <item title="Raw .vtkpipeline Page" dialog="true" skip="true">
      <description>
         On this page you can see how your pipeline structure looks.
         You could edit this file by hand but it is recommended you use the editor
         to make changes in order to keep your file valid at all times.
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
