<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<compositeCheatsheet name="g-Eclipse Cheatsheets">
   <taskGroup kind="sequence" name="Visualisation with g-Eclipse" skip="true">
      <intro>
         This set of cheat sheets will show you how to 
use g-Eclipse to visualise scientific data sets, computed on the Grid.<br/><br/>You can select a task to work on, either by following the hyperlinks offered below, or by selecting a task after expanding the tree above.<br/>
      </intro>
      <onCompletion>
         Congratulations! You have learned how to visualise scientific data from within g-Eclipse.
      </onCompletion>
      <taskGroup kind="sequence" name="Defining the VTK Pipeline" skip="true">
         <intro>
            First, you will learn how to create the VTK Pipeline file and set its content.
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            Congratulations! You have learned how to use the VTK Pipeline file creation wizard and the pipeline editor.
         </onCompletion>
         <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Creating VTK Pipeline File" skip="false">
            <intro>
               This cheatsheet describes the steps in creating VTK Pipeline file.
            </intro>
            <onCompletion>
               Congratulations! You have successfully created a VTK Pipeline file.
            </onCompletion>
            <param name="path" value="CreatingVtkPipelineFile.xml">
            </param>
         </task>
         <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Specifying VTK Pipeline Content" skip="false">
            <intro>
               This cheatsheet explanes how to set the content of the VTK Pipeline.
            </intro>
            <onCompletion>
               Congratulation! You have successfully specified the content of your VTK Pipeline.
            </onCompletion>
            <param name="path" value="SpecifyingVtkPipelineContent.xml">
            </param>
         </task>
      </taskGroup>
      <taskGroup kind="set" name="Rendering" skip="false">
         <intro>
            Next, you will learn about the two ways of rendering your data using g-Eclipse.
         </intro>
         <onCompletion>
            Congratulations! You have learned how you can use g-Eclipse to render your data.
         </onCompletion>
         <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Local Rendering" skip="false">
            <intro>
               Here you will learn how to visualise data processed and rendered on your local computer.
            </intro>
            <onCompletion>
               Congratulation! You have learned how to use g-Eclipse to visualise scientific data sets, processed and rendered on your local computer.
            </onCompletion>
            <param name="path" value="RenderingLocally.xml">
            </param>
         </task>
         <task kind="cheatsheet" name="Remote Rendering" skip="false">
            <intro>
               Here you will learn how to run the rendering job on a remote machine and visualise the results on your local computer.
            </intro>
            <onCompletion>
               Congratulation! You have learned how to visualise remotely rendered data from within g-Eclipse.
            </onCompletion>
            <param name="path" value="RenderingRemotely.xml">
            </param>
         </task>
      </taskGroup>
   </taskGroup>
</compositeCheatsheet>
